epurplemedia.co.uk 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy

Privacy

The statements on this page disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. 

**Domain:** http://www.epurplemedia.co.uk 

**Owner:**   
Parade House,  
135, The Parade High Street,  
Watford, Hertfordshire,  
WD17 1NS, United Kingdom  
Phone: +44 207 0972695  
Free Phone: 0800 097 0237 

**General Data Collection Statement:** Identifiable information is collected.  
Our website collects information and/or some information may be used to identify the website user. 

**Why do we collect information?** This Web site collects click-stream data. It represents the combination of information typically found in Web server access logs: the IP address or host name of the user's computer, the Web address of the resource requested, the time the request was made, etc. This Web site collects miscellaneous information to include Physical Contact Information, Online Contact Information, Unique Identifiers, Purchase Information, Navigation and Click-stream Data. We collect information from our visitors to complete a transaction or a Web site activity related to our business cycle which includes both of our merchants and affiliates besides end user 

**Access**

The access our website visitors are given to the information collected about them is:   
Other Identified Data: access is given to certain other identified data (e.g., users can access things such as their online account charges).

**Disputes**

If a website visitor wants to file a dispute pertaining to your websites privacy policy, the dispute will be resolved by: Individual may complain to the Web sites customer service representative for resolution of disputes regarding the use of collected data.

You may view information on our dispute resolution policies and procedures here: privacy.html

Customer support at Rupiz media Ltd. can be contacted via email at info@epurplemedial.co.uk. Please allow atleast 72 hrs for us to do the initial investigation and response. 

A visitor may verify our privacy practice here: privacy.html

Our organization responds to visitor claims by: Errors or wrongful actions arising in connection with the privacy policy will be remedied by the service. 

**Purpose**

We collect information from our visitors to complete a transaction or a website activity such as: 

  * Returning the results from a web search 
  * Forwarding an email message 
  * Placing an order 
  * Recurring activity such as providing a subscription service 
  * Allowing access to an online address book or electronic wallet. 

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of website administration; users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of research and development; users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of tailoring the site for them; users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of research, analysis and reporting but will not be used to attempt to identify them; users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of make a decision that directly affects them but will not be used to attempt to identify them; users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of contacting them for marketing of services or products (excluding telemarketing); users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of historical preservation; users are required to have their information used for this purpose.

We collect information from our visitors for the purpose of contacting them for marketing of services or products, by telephone; but users may opt-out of having their information used for this purpose.

**Recipients**

Information is collected by our website and used by our organization and/or other businesses acting as agents for our organization, or for whom our organization is acting as an agent. information will be shared with our business parteners who share our privacy policy

**Retention**

Information is retained for an indeterminate period of time. 

**Information is Collected About**

This Web site collects clickstream data. Clickstream data is expected to apply to practically all websites. It represents the combination of information typically found in Web server access logs: the IP address or hostname of the users computer, the web address of the resource requested, the time the request was made, etc. 

This Web site collects information stored in cookies to include Unique Identifiers,Navigation and Click-stream Data,Demographic and Socioeconomic Data,Preference Data,Location Data 

This Web site keeps track of the interactions it has with website visitors other than clickstream data (i.e. account transactions) 

Cookies Policy

**1\. Information about cookies :**   
Cookies are merely text files, used to identify individual users. They are placed in computer's browser to store preferences. Cookies, are not plug ins nor are they programs. They are stored on the computer's hard drive and can be deleted at any time. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. 

Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us email address or other personal information unless a person choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. They do not contain any personal information about you. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems. 

**2\. Purpose:**   
We make very limited use of cookies. The few of the purposes are listed below: 

a. Cookies are used by us to analyse users' surfing behaviour within the web site. We use cookies to record how many people apply for our products based on our advertising campaigns. The cookie contains a unique session identifier, and contains no personal or private data. 

b. We place cookies to collect aggregate information on the number of visitors to our site and the number of pages viewed. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. 

c. It is also used for Web site and system administration, including research and development, traffic analysis, user analysis and business decision-making. 

We cannot and would not identify individuals and only use the consolidated data to help identify improvements to our site and navigation. We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. Cookies are stored on the hard drive of the user machine but cookies cannot access any other information stored on the hard drive of the user's computer or any other cookie stored on the same computer. 

**3\. Time Duration the information would be stored:**   
Cookies expire after 90 days, unless you delete them manually. 

**4\. Option to reject/ block cookies:**  
You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. You can choose not to accept cookies or delete any cookies from your computer, or to alert you every time a cookie is offered by us by changing the settings in your Internet Browser. 

You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser. Please check "Disable your Cookies" below. You can also manually remove cookies from your system. For more information on how to manually remove cookies from your system, please check "Delete your Cookies" below or lookup Cookies in your Operating System Documentation. 

**Disable your cookies:**

**For Windows Systems:**

  * Explorer 6.0 Tools - Internet options - Privacy -Setting - Manually slide the bar up to "Block All Cookies" - OK 
  * Firefox 1.0 Tools - Options - Cookies - Allow sites to set Cookies - Unmark - OK 
  * Netscape 7.1 Edit - Preferences - Privacy & Security - Cookies - Disable all cookies - OK

**For Linux System:**

  * Explorer 6.0 Tools - Internet options - Privacy -Setting - Manually slide the bar up to "Block All Cookies" - OK
  * Firefox 1.0 Tools - Options - Cookies - Allow sites to set Cookies - Unmark - OK 

**Delete your cookies:**

**For Windows System:**

  * Explorer 6.0 Tools - Internet options - General - Delete Cookies - OK 
  * Fire fox 1.0 Tools - Options - Cookies - Clear All Cookies - OK 
  * Netscape 8.1 Tool - Options - Privacy - view Cookies - Remove All Cookies - OK 

**For Linux System:**

  * Explorer 6.0 - Internet options - General - Delete Cookies - OK 
  * Firebox 1.0 Tools - Options - Cookies - Clear All Cookies - OK 

Deleting or disabling cookies options may vary according to browser and version of the system, so kindly refer to the help menu of the browser, in case you face any difficulty. 

However, you may not be able to login/surf some of the pages of the website if cookies are disabled. Please be aware that if you decline the use of cookies set by us, you will be unable to register or use the personalized areas of the site.
